

Profile Info

A passionate and enthusiastic digital marketing specialist (graphic designer, video editor. content creator)! I have been working on several projects covering a range of designed product both for client (freelance) and personal. As for client, I do digital marketing campaign, social media management, digital artwork, and digital ads campaign. As for my personal project, I have been leading, creating, and publishing contents for 360KH (Media Content) on YouTube and Facebook with 37K subscribers and 1K followers respectively.

Skills

Social Media Ads

Content Creation

Video Editing

Graphic Design

Interests

Digital Artwork

Current Events

Design

technology

Language

Khmer $\star \star \star \star \star$ English $\star \star \star \star \star$

PONG CHANNY

+855 97 721 19101 channypersonalmail@gmail.com

Digital Marketing

Phone Email

Address

Tuek Thla, Phnom Penh

Experience

Content Creator & Digital Marketing Lead Oct 2022 - Now DR Tech Co., LTD | Phnom Penh

Managing and running social media campaigns for DR Tech subsidized businesses includes entertainment business, liquor shop, and beauty clinic. Facilitate and lead media team to produce, design, and publish content. Evaluate and report progress directly to the manager boss and insightful explanation and proposal.

Digital Marketing Specialist

Jan 2022 - Oct 2022

A2A Town Cambodia I Phnom Penh

Marketing strategy - Social Media Marketing - Content Management - Graphic Design - Video Editing - School Marketing campaign, - vKirirom Pine Resort Marketing Campaign, Leading content creation team.

Social Media Executive

BIGO LIVE KH I Phnom Penh

Apr 2022 - Sept 2022

Marketing strategy - Social Media Marketing - Content Management - Content Planning - Social Media Budgeting - Graphic Design - Video Editing - Direct Marketing Campaign - Content Creation with team.

Creative Teaching Lead (Freelance) Sept 2021 - Dec 2022 SpeakTe I Phnom Penh

- Writing, reviewing, editing, and updating video content
- Using social media to promote company
- Establish campaign objectives and tasks
- Identify and solve problems
- Teach online classes instructed by management

Content Creator

Jan 2019 - Now

360KH I Phnom Penh

I am a founder of 360KH YouTube channel where I

- Lead team to produce content
- Research and formulate written content
- Design, editing, and post contents on social media

Education

Software Engineering 2017 - 2021

Kirirom Institute of Technology

High School Certificate 2009 - 2016

Jay Pritzker Academy I Siem Reap